[
    {
        "question": "作製",
        "answer": "さくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "略す",
        "answer": "りゃくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "平日",
        "answer": "へいじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "学級",
        "answer": "がっきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "担ぐ",
        "answer": "かつぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "銅",
        "answer": "どう"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り入れる",
        "answer": "とりいれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "欄",
        "answer": "らん"
    },
    {
        "question": "交差",
        "answer": "こうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "剃刀",
        "answer": "かみそり"
    },
    {
        "question": "通勤",
        "answer": "つうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "嫌がる",
        "answer": "いやがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸す",
        "answer": "むす"
    },
    {
        "question": "随筆",
        "answer": "ずいひつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝間着",
        "answer": "ねまき"
    },
    {
        "question": "広める",
        "answer": "ひろめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "回数券",
        "answer": "かいすうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "儲かる",
        "answer": "もうかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "山林",
        "answer": "さんりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "月末",
        "answer": "げつまつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "膨らます",
        "answer": "ふくらます"
    },
    {
        "question": "安易",
        "answer": "あんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "恋しい",
        "answer": "こいしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "通ずる",
        "answer": "つうずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "言い付ける",
        "answer": "いいつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "目覚し",
        "answer": "めざまし"
    },
    {
        "question": "住居",
        "answer": "じゅうきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "火口",
        "answer": "かこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "民謡",
        "answer": "みんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "錆",
        "answer": "さび"
    },
    {
        "question": "売上",
        "answer": "うりあげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "標本",
        "answer": "ひょうほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "呼び掛ける",
        "answer": "よびかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "性質",
        "answer": "せいしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "角度",
        "answer": "かくど"
    },
    {
        "question": "下品",
        "answer": "げひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "揚げる",
        "answer": "あげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "解散",
        "answer": "かいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "無限",
        "answer": "むげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "矢印",
        "answer": "やじるし"
    },
    {
        "question": "見出し",
        "answer": "みだし"
    },
    {
        "question": "損得",
        "answer": "そんとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "社会科学",
        "answer": "しゃかいかがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "改正",
        "answer": "かいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "裁縫",
        "answer": "さいほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "低下",
        "answer": "ていか"
    },
    {
        "question": "映す",
        "answer": "うつす"
    },
    {
        "question": "隙間",
        "answer": "すきま"
    },
    {
        "question": "払い戻す",
        "answer": "はらいもどす"
    },
    {
        "question": "畳む",
        "answer": "たたむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真空",
        "answer": "しんくう"
    },
    {
        "question": "宴会",
        "answer": "えんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "青白い",
        "answer": "あおじろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "呑気",
        "answer": "のんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "判子",
        "answer": "はんこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "御馳走",
        "answer": "ごちそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "鐘",
        "answer": "かね"
    },
    {
        "question": "大工",
        "answer": "だいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "刻む",
        "answer": "きざむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "迷信",
        "answer": "めいしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "月給",
        "answer": "げっきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "ミリ",
        "answer": "（メートル）"
    },
    {
        "question": "定価",
        "answer": "ていか"
    },
    {
        "question": "響き",
        "answer": "ひびき"
    },
    {
        "question": "酒場",
        "answer": "さかば"
    },
    {
        "question": "別荘",
        "answer": "べっそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "通訳",
        "answer": "つうやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "扇子",
        "answer": "せんす"
    },
    {
        "question": "食塩",
        "answer": "しょくえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "純情",
        "answer": "じゅんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "姪",
        "answer": "めい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り消す",
        "answer": "とりけす"
    },
    {
        "question": "寄せる",
        "answer": "よせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "役目",
        "answer": "やくめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "拡張",
        "answer": "かくちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "直後",
        "answer": "ちょくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "吹雪",
        "answer": "ふぶき"
    },
    {
        "question": "峠",
        "answer": "とうげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "憧れる",
        "answer": "あこがれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "水筒",
        "answer": "すいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "濡らす",
        "answer": "ぬらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "見慣れる",
        "answer": "みなれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒々しい",
        "answer": "そうぞうしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "泊める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "響く",
        "answer": "ひびく"
    },
    {
        "question": "経度",
        "answer": "けいど"
    },
    {
        "question": "回転",
        "answer": "かいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "延長",
        "answer": "えんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "御免",
        "answer": "ごめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "稀",
        "answer": "まれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "何分",
        "answer": "なにぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "納める",
        "answer": "おさめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "受話器",
        "answer": "じゅわき"
    },
    {
        "question": "訳す",
        "answer": "やくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "官庁",
        "answer": "かんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "祭日",
        "answer": "さいじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "強化",
        "answer": "きょうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "仮名",
        "answer": "かな"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾電池",
        "answer": "かんでんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "溜まる",
        "answer": "たまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "休講",
        "answer": "きゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来月",
        "answer": "さらいげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫妻",
        "answer": "ふさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "文体",
        "answer": "ぶんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "線路",
        "answer": "せんろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "古典",
        "answer": "こてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "潜る",
        "answer": "もぐる"
    },
    {
        "question": "芸能",
        "answer": "げいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "受け持つ",
        "answer": "うけもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "習字",
        "answer": "しゅうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "文脈",
        "answer": "ぶんみゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "暖まる",
        "answer": "あたたまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "太鼓",
        "answer": "たいこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "落し物",
        "answer": "おとしもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "皮膚",
        "answer": "ひふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "風呂敷",
        "answer": "ふろしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "油断",
        "answer": "ゆだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "砕ける",
        "answer": "くだける"
    },
    {
        "question": "献立",
        "answer": "こんだて"
    },
    {
        "question": "部品",
        "answer": "ぶひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "軟らかい",
        "answer": "やわらかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "来日",
        "answer": "らいにち"
    },
    {
        "question": "制作",
        "answer": "せいさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来年",
        "answer": "さらいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "測る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "気を付ける",
        "answer": "きをつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "付近",
        "answer": "ふきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "作る/造る",
        "answer": "つくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大小",
        "answer": "だいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "話し掛ける",
        "answer": "はなしかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝わる",
        "answer": "つたわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "盆",
        "answer": "ぼん"
    },
    {
        "question": "兵隊",
        "answer": "へいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "刷る",
        "answer": "する"
    },
    {
        "question": "寒帯",
        "answer": "かんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "定休日",
        "answer": "ていきゅうび"
    },
    {
        "question": "光線",
        "answer": "こうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "地質",
        "answer": "ちしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "発揮",
        "answer": "はっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "通路",
        "answer": "つうろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "住まい",
        "answer": "すまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "整う",
        "answer": "ととのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お帰り",
        "answer": "おかえり"
    },
    {
        "question": "垣根",
        "answer": "かきね"
    },
    {
        "question": "坊さん",
        "answer": "ぼうさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "休息",
        "answer": "きゅうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "一昨日",
        "answer": "いっさくじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "特殊",
        "answer": "とくしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "けれど/けれども",
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "question": "混合",
        "answer": "こんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方面",
        "answer": "ほうめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "中旬",
        "answer": "ちゅうじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "言付ける",
        "answer": "ことづける"
    },
    {
        "question": "蹴る",
        "answer": "ける"
    },
    {
        "question": "静まる",
        "answer": "しずまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "逃がす",
        "answer": "にがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "渇く",
        "answer": "かわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "紺",
        "answer": "こん"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝台",
        "answer": "しんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝む",
        "answer": "おがむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "打ち消す",
        "answer": "うちけす"
    },
    {
        "question": "繋げる",
        "answer": "つなげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "若々しい",
        "answer": "わかわかしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "個体",
        "answer": "こたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "煙突",
        "answer": "えんとつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸気",
        "answer": "じょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "括弧",
        "answer": "かっこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "散る",
        "answer": "ちる"
    },
    {
        "question": "張り切る",
        "answer": "はりきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏口",
        "answer": "うらぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "務める",
        "answer": "つとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "賞金",
        "answer": "しょうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "月日",
        "answer": "つきひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "謙虚",
        "answer": "けんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒がしい",
        "answer": "さわがしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "強気",
        "answer": "つよき"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い掛けない",
        "answer": "おもいがけない"
    },
    {
        "question": "揉む",
        "answer": "もむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "腰掛け",
        "answer": "こしかけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "消防署",
        "answer": "しょうぼうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "回り道",
        "answer": "まわりみち"
    },
    {
        "question": "物凄い",
        "answer": "ものすごい"
    },
    {
        "question": "初旬",
        "answer": "しょじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "順序",
        "answer": "じゅんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片付く",
        "answer": "かたづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "終点",
        "answer": "しゅうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "餅",
        "answer": "もち"
    },
    {
        "question": "観念",
        "answer": "かんねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "這う",
        "answer": "はう"
    },
    {
        "question": "耕す",
        "answer": "たがやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "蓋",
        "answer": "ふた"
    },
    {
        "question": "基準",
        "answer": "きじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恩恵",
        "answer": "おんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "明き",
        "answer": "あき"
    },
    {
        "question": "演劇",
        "answer": "えんげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "詰まる",
        "answer": "つまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "締め切る",
        "answer": "しめきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "消極的",
        "answer": "しょうきょくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "更ける",
        "answer": "ふける"
    },
    {
        "question": "草履",
        "answer": "ぞうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "児童",
        "answer": "じどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "出迎える",
        "answer": "でむかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "方針",
        "answer": "ほうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "引越し",
        "answer": "ひっこし"
    },
    {
        "question": "危うい",
        "answer": "あやうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "全般",
        "answer": "ぜんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "対照",
        "answer": "たいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "総理大臣",
        "answer": "そうりだいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "縮小",
        "answer": "しゅくしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "虹",
        "answer": "にじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "扇ぐ",
        "answer": "あおぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "探る",
        "answer": "さぐる"
    },
    {
        "question": "恵まれる",
        "answer": "めぐまれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "請う",
        "answer": "こう"
    },
    {
        "question": "御中",
        "answer": "おんちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "飢饉",
        "answer": "ききん"
    },
    {
        "question": "漁業",
        "answer": "ぎょぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人命",
        "answer": "じんめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "効力",
        "answer": "こうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "四角い",
        "answer": "しかくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗車",
        "answer": "じょうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "払い込む",
        "answer": "はらいこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鑑賞",
        "answer": "かんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "荒い",
        "answer": "あらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "人文科学",
        "answer": "じんぶんかがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "怪しい",
        "answer": "あやしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "点々",
        "answer": "てんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "絵の具",
        "answer": "えのぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "東西",
        "answer": "とうざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "果して",
        "answer": "はたして"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り出す",
        "answer": "とりだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "物騒",
        "answer": "ぶっそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "悔やむ",
        "answer": "くやむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "農薬",
        "answer": "のうやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "重ねる",
        "answer": "かさねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "錆びる",
        "answer": "さびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "部首",
        "answer": "ぶしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "深まる",
        "answer": "ふかまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "原稿",
        "answer": "げんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "初級",
        "answer": "しょきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "肌着",
        "answer": "はだぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "長男",
        "answer": "ちょうなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "先祖",
        "answer": "せんぞ"
    },
    {
        "question": "神様",
        "answer": "かみさま"
    },
    {
        "question": "早口",
        "answer": "はやくち"
    },
    {
        "question": "口実",
        "answer": "こうじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "祭る",
        "answer": "まつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "屋外",
        "answer": "おくがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "退く",
        "answer": "どく"
    },
    {
        "question": "延びる",
        "answer": "のびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "芯",
        "answer": "しん"
    },
    {
        "question": "免税",
        "answer": "めんぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "出合い",
        "answer": "であい"
    },
    {
        "question": "並木",
        "answer": "なみき"
    },
    {
        "question": "縮める",
        "answer": "ちぢめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "発つ",
        "answer": "たつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "広げる",
        "answer": "ひろげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "競馬",
        "answer": "けいば"
    },
    {
        "question": "余る",
        "answer": "あまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "永い",
        "answer": "ながい"
    },
    {
        "question": "測定",
        "answer": "そくてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "唇",
        "answer": "くちびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "捜す",
        "answer": "さがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "北極",
        "answer": "ほっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "退ける",
        "answer": "どける"
    },
    {
        "question": "険しい",
        "answer": "けわしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "実力",
        "answer": "じつりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "附属",
        "answer": "ふぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "活力",
        "answer": "かつりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "転々",
        "answer": "てんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "助教授",
        "answer": "じょきょうじゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宣伝",
        "answer": "せんでん"
    },
    {
        "question": "食器",
        "answer": "しょっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "消耗",
        "answer": "しょうもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "有無",
        "answer": "うむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾燥",
        "answer": "かんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "定期券",
        "answer": "ていきけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "堀",
        "answer": "ほり"
    },
    {
        "question": "言葉遣い",
        "answer": "ことばづかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "算盤",
        "answer": "そろばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "潰す",
        "answer": "つぶす"
    },
    {
        "question": "狡い",
        "answer": "ずるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "無数",
        "answer": "むすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "父母",
        "answer": "ふぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "謎謎",
        "answer": "なぞなぞ"
    },
    {
        "question": "欲張り",
        "answer": "よくばり"
    },
    {
        "question": "論ずる",
        "answer": "ろんずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "突き当たり",
        "answer": "つきあたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "射す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "好き嫌い",
        "answer": "すききらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "教わる",
        "answer": "おそわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "分布",
        "answer": "ぶんぷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "発射",
        "answer": "はっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "治める",
        "answer": "おさめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "生ずる",
        "answer": "しょうずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "足袋",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "question": "勇ましい",
        "answer": "いさましい"
    },
    {
        "question": "倣う",
        "answer": "ならう"
    },
    {
        "question": "段階",
        "answer": "だんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "交替",
        "answer": "こうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "図鑑",
        "answer": "ずかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "学会",
        "answer": "がっかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "周辺",
        "answer": "しゅうへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "水分",
        "answer": "すいぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "以後",
        "answer": "いご"
    },
    {
        "question": "中味",
        "answer": "なかみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "傑作",
        "answer": "けっさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "炊事",
        "answer": "すいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "先々週",
        "answer": "せんせんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "役者",
        "answer": "やくしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "形容詞",
        "answer": "けいようし"
    },
    {
        "question": "交ざる",
        "answer": "まざる"
    },
    {
        "question": "見本",
        "answer": "みほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛び込む",
        "answer": "とびこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "潰れる",
        "answer": "つぶれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "項目",
        "answer": "こうもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "包帯",
        "answer": "ほうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "写生",
        "answer": "しゃせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "洋品店",
        "answer": "ようひんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "同格",
        "answer": "どうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "長引く",
        "answer": "ながびく"
    },
    {
        "question": "清書",
        "answer": "せいしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "時速",
        "answer": "じそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "手首",
        "answer": "てくび"
    },
    {
        "question": "民間",
        "answer": "みんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "実績",
        "answer": "じっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "熟語",
        "answer": "じゅくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "有難い",
        "answer": "ありがたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝染",
        "answer": "でんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "弱点",
        "answer": "じゃくてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "俳句",
        "answer": "はいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "炒る",
        "answer": "いる"
    },
    {
        "question": "飾り",
        "answer": "かざり"
    },
    {
        "question": "目立つ",
        "answer": "めだつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "打合せ",
        "answer": "うちあわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "清い",
        "answer": "きよい"
    },
    {
        "question": "前後",
        "answer": "ぜんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "学科",
        "answer": "がっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "留まる",
        "answer": "とどまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "形容動詞",
        "answer": "けいようどうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "睨む",
        "answer": "にらむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "海洋",
        "answer": "かいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蕎麦",
        "answer": "そば"
    },
    {
        "question": "梯子",
        "answer": "はしご"
    },
    {
        "question": "定員",
        "answer": "ていいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "延ばす",
        "answer": "のばす"
    },
    {
        "question": "断定",
        "answer": "だんてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "格別",
        "answer": "かくべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "重役",
        "answer": "じゅうやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱する",
        "answer": "ねっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "残らず",
        "answer": "のこらず"
    },
    {
        "question": "割算",
        "answer": "わりざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "売行き",
        "answer": "うれゆき"
    },
    {
        "question": "転がす",
        "answer": "ころがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "牧畜",
        "answer": "ぼくちく"
    },
    {
        "question": "狙う",
        "answer": "ねらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "送別",
        "answer": "そうべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "次ぐ",
        "answer": "つぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "原産",
        "answer": "げんさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "採る",
        "answer": "とる"
    },
    {
        "question": "跳ねる",
        "answer": "はねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "複数",
        "answer": "ふくすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "吐き気",
        "answer": "はきけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "退院",
        "answer": "たいいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "規律",
        "answer": "きりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "香水",
        "answer": "こうすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "膨らむ",
        "answer": "ふくらむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "産地",
        "answer": "さんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "着替え",
        "answer": "きがえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "襖",
        "answer": "ふすま"
    },
    {
        "question": "彫刻",
        "answer": "ちょうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "具える",
        "answer": "そなえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "必需品",
        "answer": "ひつじゅひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "点く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "滑れる",
        "answer": "ずれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "桁",
        "answer": "けた"
    },
    {
        "question": "改める",
        "answer": "あらためる"
    },
    {
        "question": "解答",
        "answer": "かいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日の入り",
        "answer": "ひのいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "公共",
        "answer": "こうきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "欧米",
        "answer": "おうべい"
    },
    {
        "question": "発売",
        "answer": "はつばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "生年月日",
        "answer": "せいねんがっぴ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出来上がる",
        "answer": "できあがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "限度",
        "answer": "げんど"
    },
    {
        "question": "生存",
        "answer": "せいぞん"
    },
    {
        "question": "入社",
        "answer": "にゅうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "本来",
        "answer": "ほんらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "突っ込む",
        "answer": "つっこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "診断",
        "answer": "しんだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "薄暗い",
        "answer": "うすぐらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一斉",
        "answer": "いっせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "剥く",
        "answer": "むく"
    },
    {
        "question": "分解",
        "answer": "ぶんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "理科",
        "answer": "りか"
    },
    {
        "question": "半島",
        "answer": "はんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "社説",
        "answer": "しゃせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "慶ぶ",
        "answer": "よろこぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "合流",
        "answer": "ごうりゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "作者",
        "answer": "さくしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "妨げる",
        "answer": "さまたげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "固い",
        "answer": "かたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "性別",
        "answer": "せいべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "折角",
        "answer": "せっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "座敷",
        "answer": "ざしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "商社",
        "answer": "しょうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "代る",
        "answer": "かわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "縛る",
        "answer": "しばる"
    },
    {
        "question": "儀式",
        "answer": "ぎしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "小遣い",
        "answer": "こづかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "敷地",
        "answer": "しきち"
    },
    {
        "question": "不通",
        "answer": "ふつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "関西",
        "answer": "かんさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "裂く",
        "answer": "さく"
    },
    {
        "question": "比較的",
        "answer": "ひかくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "御手洗",
        "answer": "おてあらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "飽くまで",
        "answer": "あくまで"
    },
    {
        "question": "団地",
        "answer": "だんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "腰掛ける",
        "answer": "こしかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "口紅",
        "answer": "くちべに"
    },
    {
        "question": "水平線",
        "answer": "すいへいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "挙げる",
        "answer": "あげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "慶び",
        "answer": "よろこび"
    },
    {
        "question": "現に",
        "answer": "げんに"
    },
    {
        "question": "過剰",
        "answer": "かじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "在学",
        "answer": "ざいがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "題名",
        "answer": "だいめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "無沙汰",
        "answer": "ぶさた"
    },
    {
        "question": "生る",
        "answer": "なる"
    },
    {
        "question": "お出掛け",
        "answer": "おでかけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集金",
        "answer": "しゅうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "標準",
        "answer": "ひょうじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶岩",
        "answer": "ようがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "中間",
        "answer": "ちゅうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "木材",
        "answer": "もくざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "揃える",
        "answer": "そろえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "創作",
        "answer": "そうさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "誓う",
        "answer": "ちかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "雨戸",
        "answer": "あまど"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ白",
        "answer": "まっしろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "散らかる",
        "answer": "ちらかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "粗い",
        "answer": "あらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "茶碗",
        "answer": "ちゃわん"
    },
    {
        "question": "羨む",
        "answer": "うらやむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "課程",
        "answer": "かてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "巡る",
        "answer": "めぐる"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛皮",
        "answer": "けがわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "地盤",
        "answer": "じばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "天皇",
        "answer": "てんのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "敷く",
        "answer": "しく"
    },
    {
        "question": "垂直",
        "answer": "すいちょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "空想",
        "answer": "くうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "留守番",
        "answer": "るすばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "牧場",
        "answer": "ぼくじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "全集",
        "answer": "ぜんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "分かれる",
        "answer": "わかれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "敬語",
        "answer": "けいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "動作",
        "answer": "どうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰す",
        "answer": "かえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "小父さん",
        "answer": "おじさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "井戸",
        "answer": "いど"
    },
    {
        "question": "絶えず",
        "answer": "たえず"
    },
    {
        "question": "掻く",
        "answer": "かく"
    },
    {
        "question": "確率",
        "answer": "かくりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "岬",
        "answer": "みさき"
    },
    {
        "question": "大分",
        "answer": "だいぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "図表",
        "answer": "ずひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "しいんと",
        "answer": "（する）"
    },
    {
        "question": "名字",
        "answer": "みょうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "連合",
        "answer": "れんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "商店",
        "answer": "しょうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "役所",
        "answer": "やくしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "直通",
        "answer": "ちょくつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "悠々",
        "answer": "ゆうゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "手洗い",
        "answer": "てあらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "放れる",
        "answer": "はなれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "杉",
        "answer": "すぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不潔",
        "answer": "ふけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "間隔",
        "answer": "かんかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾らか",
        "answer": "なだらか"
    },
    {
        "question": "応用",
        "answer": "おうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "酌む",
        "answer": "くむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "怠る",
        "answer": "おこたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "後輩",
        "answer": "こうはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "蛍光灯",
        "answer": "けいこうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "坊っちゃん",
        "answer": "ぼっちゃん"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕立",
        "answer": "ゆうだち"
    },
    {
        "question": "休養",
        "answer": "きゅうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "釘",
        "answer": "くぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "甚だしい",
        "answer": "はなはだしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "学術",
        "answer": "がくじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "押える",
        "answer": "おさえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕刊",
        "answer": "ゆうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "引出す",
        "answer": "ひきだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "間も無く",
        "answer": "まもなく"
    },
    {
        "question": "尖る",
        "answer": "とがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "素人",
        "answer": "しろうと"
    },
    {
        "question": "観測",
        "answer": "かんそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "下車",
        "answer": "げしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "親類",
        "answer": "しんるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "番地",
        "answer": "ばんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "英和",
        "answer": "えいわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "原理",
        "answer": "げんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "地点",
        "answer": "ちてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "開会",
        "answer": "かいかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "意地悪",
        "answer": "いじわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "照る",
        "answer": "てる"
    },
    {
        "question": "汁",
        "answer": "しる"
    },
    {
        "question": "拭く",
        "answer": "ふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "血液",
        "answer": "けつえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "外部",
        "answer": "がいぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "衣食住",
        "answer": "いしょくじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "別々",
        "answer": "べつべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "固まる",
        "answer": "かたまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "正門",
        "answer": "せいもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文芸",
        "answer": "ぶんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "椀",
        "answer": "わん"
    },
    {
        "question": "因る",
        "answer": "よる"
    },
    {
        "question": "終了",
        "answer": "しゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "卑怯",
        "answer": "ひきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "申請",
        "answer": "しんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "煮る",
        "answer": "にる"
    },
    {
        "question": "だいいち",
        "answer": "（副）"
    },
    {
        "question": "当番",
        "answer": "とうばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "承る",
        "answer": "うけたまわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "通知",
        "answer": "つうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "純粋",
        "answer": "じゅんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "炊く",
        "answer": "たく"
    },
    {
        "question": "引力",
        "answer": "いんりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "瀬戸物",
        "answer": "せともの"
    },
    {
        "question": "大学院",
        "answer": "だいがくいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "派手",
        "answer": "はで"
    },
    {
        "question": "見直す",
        "answer": "みなおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "出張",
        "answer": "しゅっちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "髭",
        "answer": "ひげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "碗",
        "answer": "わん"
    },
    {
        "question": "背負う",
        "answer": "せおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "並行",
        "answer": "へいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "挿す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "友好",
        "answer": "ゆうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "洗剤",
        "answer": "せんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "公衆",
        "answer": "こうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "心当たり",
        "answer": "こころあたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "売り切れる",
        "answer": "うりきれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "焦がす",
        "answer": "こがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "付合う",
        "answer": "つきあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷やす",
        "answer": "ひやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "国王",
        "answer": "こくおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "卒直",
        "answer": "そっちょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "領収",
        "answer": "りょうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "行事",
        "answer": "ぎょうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "方言",
        "answer": "ほうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "存じる",
        "answer": "ぞんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "水曜",
        "answer": "すいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "佚",
        "answer": "いつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "失恋",
        "answer": "しつれん"
    },
    {
        "question": "実習",
        "answer": "じっしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "針金",
        "answer": "はりがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "始終",
        "answer": "しじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝見",
        "answer": "はいけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "日日",
        "answer": "ひにち"
    },
    {
        "question": "蚊",
        "answer": "か"
    },
    {
        "question": "西暦",
        "answer": "せいれき"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶かす",
        "answer": "とかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "治す",
        "answer": "なおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "家屋",
        "answer": "かおく"
    },
    {
        "question": "表紙",
        "answer": "ひょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "又は",
        "answer": "または"
    },
    {
        "question": "応援",
        "answer": "おうえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷ます",
        "answer": "さます"
    },
    {
        "question": "激増",
        "answer": "げきぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "以降",
        "answer": "いこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "何々",
        "answer": "なになに"
    },
    {
        "question": "手入れ",
        "answer": "ていれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名詞",
        "answer": "めいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "県庁",
        "answer": "けんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "点数",
        "answer": "てんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "売り切れ",
        "answer": "うりきれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "客間",
        "answer": "きゃくま"
    },
    {
        "question": "流域",
        "answer": "りゅういき"
    },
    {
        "question": "停止",
        "answer": "ていし"
    },
    {
        "question": "向う",
        "answer": "むかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "卸す",
        "answer": "おろす"
    },
    {
        "question": "過失",
        "answer": "かしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "枯れる",
        "answer": "かれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "長方形",
        "answer": "ちょうほうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "書取",
        "answer": "かきとり"
    },
    {
        "question": "糊",
        "answer": "のり"
    },
    {
        "question": "纏まる",
        "answer": "まとまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "相撲",
        "answer": "すもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "分量",
        "answer": "ぶんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "加速度",
        "answer": "かそくど"
    },
    {
        "question": "混ざる",
        "answer": "まざる"
    },
    {
        "question": "好き好き",
        "answer": "すきずき"
    },
    {
        "question": "余所",
        "answer": "よそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "彫る",
        "answer": "ほる"
    },
    {
        "question": "親指",
        "answer": "おやゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "容器",
        "answer": "ようき"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ繰り返る",
        "answer": "ひっくりかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "秤",
        "answer": "はかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "看病",
        "answer": "かんびょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "瓦",
        "answer": "かわら"
    },
    {
        "question": "消毒",
        "answer": "しょうどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大して",
        "answer": "たいして"
    },
    {
        "question": "述語",
        "answer": "じゅつご"
    },
    {
        "question": "加速",
        "answer": "かそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "詫びる",
        "answer": "わびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "手前",
        "answer": "てまえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "仮定",
        "answer": "かてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "惜しい",
        "answer": "おしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬局",
        "answer": "やっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "驚かす",
        "answer": "おどろかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "出入口",
        "answer": "でいりぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "分る",
        "answer": "わかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "争う",
        "answer": "あらそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "酔っ払い",
        "answer": "よっぱらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "漁師",
        "answer": "りょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "標識",
        "answer": "ひょうしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "不規則",
        "answer": "ふきそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "見付かる",
        "answer": "みつかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "生き生き",
        "answer": "いきいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "飢える",
        "answer": "うえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "出迎え",
        "answer": "でむかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿る",
        "answer": "しめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "塞がる",
        "answer": "ふさがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "曲線",
        "answer": "きょくせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺さる",
        "answer": "ささる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷凍",
        "answer": "れいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "形式",
        "answer": "けいしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "消化",
        "answer": "しょうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "煙い",
        "answer": "けむい"
    },
    {
        "question": "暖める",
        "answer": "あたためる"
    },
    {
        "question": "爪",
        "answer": "つめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐縮",
        "answer": "きょうしゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "電球",
        "answer": "でんきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人通り",
        "answer": "ひとどおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "粒",
        "answer": "つぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "体制",
        "answer": "たいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "着せる",
        "answer": "きせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "円周",
        "answer": "えんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "存ずる",
        "answer": "ぞんずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "仕上がる",
        "answer": "しあがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "縫う",
        "answer": "ぬう"
    },
    {
        "question": "半径",
        "answer": "はんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "割引",
        "answer": "わりびき"
    },
    {
        "question": "物差し",
        "answer": "ものさし"
    },
    {
        "question": "句読点",
        "answer": "くとうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "塞ぐ",
        "answer": "ふさぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "火傷",
        "answer": "やけど"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗換",
        "answer": "のりかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "商業",
        "answer": "しょうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "間接",
        "answer": "かんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "写る",
        "answer": "うつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "重力",
        "answer": "じゅうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "手帳",
        "answer": "てちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "焚く",
        "answer": "たく"
    },
    {
        "question": "箒",
        "answer": "ほうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "編む",
        "answer": "あむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "測量",
        "answer": "そくりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "殻",
        "answer": "から"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼児",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "重たい",
        "answer": "おもたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "会館",
        "answer": "かいかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い込む",
        "answer": "おもいこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "胡椒",
        "answer": "こしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "零点",
        "answer": "れいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "磁石",
        "answer": "じしゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "努める",
        "answer": "つとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "目上",
        "answer": "めうえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "近寄る",
        "answer": "ちかよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "筆記",
        "answer": "ひっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "見舞う",
        "answer": "みまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "心身",
        "answer": "しんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い付く",
        "answer": "おもいつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "顕微鏡",
        "answer": "けんびきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "下町",
        "answer": "したまち"
    },
    {
        "question": "水滴",
        "answer": "すいてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "領事",
        "answer": "りょうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "祖先",
        "answer": "そせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "換気",
        "answer": "かんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "信ずる",
        "answer": "しんずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "透き通る",
        "answer": "すきとおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "有料",
        "answer": "ゆうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "娯楽",
        "answer": "ごらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎い",
        "answer": "にくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "汲む",
        "answer": "くむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "茶色い",
        "answer": "ちゃいろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "追い掛ける",
        "answer": "おいかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "農産物",
        "answer": "のうさんぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "行列",
        "answer": "ぎょうれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "改札",
        "answer": "かいさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾杯",
        "answer": "かんぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "歌謡",
        "answer": "かよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "用語",
        "answer": "ようご"
    },
    {
        "question": "見掛け",
        "answer": "みかけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "清む",
        "answer": "すむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "掃く",
        "answer": "はく"
    },
    {
        "question": "接続",
        "answer": "せつぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸血",
        "answer": "ゆけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全身",
        "answer": "ぜんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "上級",
        "answer": "じょうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "煮える",
        "answer": "にえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "編物",
        "answer": "あみもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "崩す",
        "answer": "くずす"
    },
    {
        "question": "締切",
        "answer": "しめきり"
    },
    {
        "question": "縞",
        "answer": "しま"
    },
    {
        "question": "独り言",
        "answer": "ひとりごと"
    },
    {
        "question": "整備",
        "answer": "せいび"
    },
    {
        "question": "郵送",
        "answer": "ゆうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸し暑い",
        "answer": "むしあつい"
    },
    {
        "question": "起床",
        "answer": "きしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "釣り合う",
        "answer": "つりあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "殖える",
        "answer": "ふえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "竹",
        "answer": "たけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "醜い",
        "answer": "みにくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "滝",
        "answer": "たき"
    },
    {
        "question": "養分",
        "answer": "ようぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "器具",
        "answer": "きぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "散らかす",
        "answer": "ちらかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "明け方",
        "answer": "あけがた"
    },
    {
        "question": "お代わり",
        "answer": "おかわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "瞳",
        "answer": "ひとみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名刺",
        "answer": "めいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "紅葉",
        "answer": "こうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "手拭い",
        "answer": "てぬぐい"
    },
    {
        "question": "干す",
        "answer": "ほす"
    },
    {
        "question": "妥当",
        "answer": "だとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉会",
        "answer": "へいかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "座布団",
        "answer": "ざぶとん"
    },
    {
        "question": "性能",
        "answer": "せいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蝋燭",
        "answer": "ろうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ暗",
        "answer": "まっくら"
    },
    {
        "question": "平凡",
        "answer": "へいぼん"
    },
    {
        "question": "重体",
        "answer": "じゅうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "書道",
        "answer": "しょどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "床の間",
        "answer": "とこのま"
    },
    {
        "question": "引き止める",
        "answer": "ひきとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "省略",
        "answer": "しょうりゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "続々",
        "answer": "ぞくぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "実る",
        "answer": "みのる"
    },
    {
        "question": "力強い",
        "answer": "ちからづよい"
    },
    {
        "question": "意義",
        "answer": "いぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "素質",
        "answer": "そしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "交ぜる",
        "answer": "まぜる"
    },
    {
        "question": "回数",
        "answer": "かいすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "感激",
        "answer": "かんげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "送り仮名",
        "answer": "おくりがな"
    },
    {
        "question": "催し",
        "answer": "もよおし"
    },
    {
        "question": "咥える",
        "answer": "くわえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "予備",
        "answer": "よび"
    },
    {
        "question": "体系",
        "answer": "たいけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶数",
        "answer": "ぐうすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "伯母さん",
        "answer": "おばさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "花火",
        "answer": "はなび"
    },
    {
        "question": "湧く",
        "answer": "わく"
    },
    {
        "question": "煎る",
        "answer": "いる"
    },
    {
        "question": "所々",
        "answer": "ところどころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "広さ",
        "answer": "ひろさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "係わる",
        "answer": "かかわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "女の人",
        "answer": "おんなのひと"
    },
    {
        "question": "叔母さん",
        "answer": "おばさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "床屋",
        "answer": "とこや"
    },
    {
        "question": "南北",
        "answer": "なんぼく"
    },
    {
        "question": "万歳",
        "answer": "ばんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "却って",
        "answer": "かえって"
    },
    {
        "question": "修繕",
        "answer": "しゅうぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "点ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "遭う",
        "answer": "あう"
    },
    {
        "question": "時間割",
        "answer": "じかんわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "応対",
        "answer": "おうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "政党",
        "answer": "せいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "枚数",
        "answer": "まいすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "只",
        "answer": "ただ"
    },
    {
        "question": "面倒臭い",
        "answer": "めんどうくさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "成立",
        "answer": "せいりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉢",
        "answer": "はち"
    },
    {
        "question": "統一",
        "answer": "とういつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "直径",
        "answer": "ちょっけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "受取",
        "answer": "うけとり"
    },
    {
        "question": "国立",
        "answer": "こくりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "方角",
        "answer": "ほうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "羽根",
        "answer": "はね"
    },
    {
        "question": "期限",
        "answer": "きげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "浮ぶ",
        "answer": "うかぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "森林",
        "answer": "しんりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "防止",
        "answer": "ぼうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "地味",
        "answer": "じみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦情",
        "answer": "くじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "学年",
        "answer": "がくねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "超過",
        "answer": "ちょうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "増減",
        "answer": "ぞうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "直前",
        "answer": "ちょくぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "公正",
        "answer": "こうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲良し",
        "answer": "なかよし"
    },
    {
        "question": "録音",
        "answer": "ろくおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "地名",
        "answer": "ちめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎む",
        "answer": "にくむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "手続き",
        "answer": "てつづき"
    },
    {
        "question": "応接",
        "answer": "おうせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "送料",
        "answer": "そうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空っぽ",
        "answer": "からっぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "短期",
        "answer": "たんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "回答",
        "answer": "かいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "幾分",
        "answer": "いくぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "見学",
        "answer": "けんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "倉庫",
        "answer": "そうこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "甘やかす",
        "answer": "あまやかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "通用",
        "answer": "つうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組合せ",
        "answer": "くみあわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏返す",
        "answer": "うらがえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶け込む",
        "answer": "とけこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "診る",
        "answer": "みる"
    },
    {
        "question": "濁る",
        "answer": "にごる"
    },
    {
        "question": "凹む",
        "answer": "へこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自衛",
        "answer": "じえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "引分け",
        "answer": "ひきわけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "方程式",
        "answer": "ほうていしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "通帳",
        "answer": "つうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄橋",
        "answer": "てっきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "思いっ切り",
        "answer": "おもいっきり"
    },
    {
        "question": "大層",
        "answer": "たいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "纏める",
        "answer": "まとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸送",
        "answer": "ゆそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "開放",
        "answer": "かいほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "漢和",
        "answer": "かんわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貸し出し",
        "answer": "かしだし"
    },
    {
        "question": "謙遜",
        "answer": "けんそん"
    },
    {
        "question": "目安",
        "answer": "めやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "出勤",
        "answer": "しゅっきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "正味",
        "answer": "しょうみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "果実",
        "answer": "かじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "五十音",
        "answer": "ごじゅうおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "偉い",
        "answer": "えらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "工夫",
        "answer": "くふう"
    },
    {
        "question": "南極",
        "answer": "なんきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "往復",
        "answer": "おうふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "日課",
        "answer": "にっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "一通り",
        "answer": "ひととおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "頼もしい",
        "answer": "たのもしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "箸",
        "answer": "はし"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜行",
        "answer": "やこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "蘇る",
        "answer": "よみがえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "雑巾",
        "answer": "ぞうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貯蔵",
        "answer": "ちょぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "小指",
        "answer": "こゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "浮く",
        "answer": "うく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大凡",
        "answer": "おおよそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "文献",
        "answer": "ぶんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溜息",
        "answer": "ためいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "伯父さん",
        "answer": "おじさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "分数",
        "answer": "ぶんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "預かる",
        "answer": "あずかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "あひら",
        "answer": "あひら"
    },
    {
        "question": "童話",
        "answer": "どうわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "重なる",
        "answer": "かさなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "注す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "構造",
        "answer": "こうぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日の出",
        "answer": "ひので"
    },
    {
        "question": "皮肉",
        "answer": "ひにく"
    },
    {
        "question": "校庭",
        "answer": "こうてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "攻める",
        "answer": "せめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "農村",
        "answer": "のうそん"
    },
    {
        "question": "真似る",
        "answer": "まねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "囁く",
        "answer": "ささやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "嗅ぐ",
        "answer": "かぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一定",
        "answer": "いってい"
    },
    {
        "question": "威張る",
        "answer": "いばる"
    },
    {
        "question": "勝負",
        "answer": "しょうぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬缶",
        "answer": "やかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "温泉",
        "answer": "おんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "掏摸",
        "answer": "すり"
    },
    {
        "question": "綱",
        "answer": "つな"
    },
    {
        "question": "水蒸気",
        "answer": "すいじょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "俄",
        "answer": "にわか"
    },
    {
        "question": "植木",
        "answer": "うえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "司会",
        "answer": "しかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "青少年",
        "answer": "せいしょうねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "職人",
        "answer": "しょくにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "基盤",
        "answer": "きばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "先程",
        "answer": "さきほど"
    },
    {
        "question": "強引",
        "answer": "ごういん"
    },
    {
        "question": "縮む",
        "answer": "ちぢむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "両側",
        "answer": "りょうがわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "緩い",
        "answer": "ゆるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "改めて",
        "answer": "あらためて"
    },
    {
        "question": "代える",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "言い出す",
        "answer": "いいだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "教養",
        "answer": "きょうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "入れ物",
        "answer": "いれもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "栓",
        "answer": "せん"
    },
    {
        "question": "御覧",
        "answer": "ごらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "園芸",
        "answer": "えんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "調節",
        "answer": "ちょうせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "お手伝いさん",
        "answer": "おてつだいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "循環",
        "answer": "じゅんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文房具",
        "answer": "ぶんぼうぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "挟む",
        "answer": "はさむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "死体",
        "answer": "したい"
    },
    {
        "question": "主役",
        "answer": "しゅやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "調味料",
        "answer": "ちょうみりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "挟まる",
        "answer": "はさまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "容積",
        "answer": "ようせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "組み立てる",
        "answer": "くみたてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "破れる",
        "answer": "やぶれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "艶",
        "answer": "つや"
    },
    {
        "question": "濃度",
        "answer": "のうど"
    },
    {
        "question": "地下水",
        "answer": "ちかすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "的確",
        "answer": "てきかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "書籍",
        "answer": "しょせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "差し支え",
        "answer": "さしつかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "短編",
        "answer": "たんぺん"
    },
    {
        "question": "透明",
        "answer": "とうめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "継続",
        "answer": "けいぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "私鉄",
        "answer": "してつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "厚かましい",
        "answer": "あつかましい"
    },
    {
        "question": "快晴",
        "answer": "かいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒸発",
        "answer": "じょうはつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "登場",
        "answer": "とうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "絞る",
        "answer": "しぼる"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ繰り返す",
        "answer": "ひっくりかえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "日当たり",
        "answer": "ひあたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "長所",
        "answer": "ちょうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "地帯",
        "answer": "ちたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "可決",
        "answer": "かけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "新幹線",
        "answer": "しんかんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "実用",
        "answer": "じつよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "電池",
        "answer": "でんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "跳ぶ",
        "answer": "とぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "先端",
        "answer": "せんたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "気圧",
        "answer": "きあつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤道",
        "answer": "せきどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "高める",
        "answer": "たかめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "日陰",
        "answer": "ひかげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "映る",
        "answer": "うつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "合同",
        "answer": "ごうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "編集",
        "answer": "へんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "命ずる",
        "answer": "めいずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "統計",
        "answer": "とうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "満員",
        "answer": "まんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "中性",
        "answer": "ちゅうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "早速",
        "answer": "さっそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "原始",
        "answer": "げんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "三日月",
        "answer": "みかづき"
    },
    {
        "question": "塵紙",
        "answer": "ちりがみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "知人",
        "answer": "ちじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "心得る",
        "answer": "こころえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠足",
        "answer": "えんそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "追い越す",
        "answer": "おいこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "日用品",
        "answer": "にちようひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "醤油",
        "answer": "しょうゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "工芸",
        "answer": "こうげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "受験",
        "answer": "じゅけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "雑音",
        "answer": "ざつおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "剃る",
        "answer": "そる"
    },
    {
        "question": "火山",
        "answer": "かざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "散らす",
        "answer": "ちらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "判事",
        "answer": "はんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "東洋",
        "answer": "とうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "書店",
        "answer": "しょてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝巻",
        "answer": "ねまき"
    },
    {
        "question": "割と",
        "answer": "わりと"
    },
    {
        "question": "目指す",
        "answer": "めざす"
    },
    {
        "question": "停電",
        "answer": "ていでん"
    },
    {
        "question": "従姉妹",
        "answer": "いとこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "下書き",
        "answer": "したがき"
    },
    {
        "question": "面接",
        "answer": "めんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "手頃",
        "answer": "てごろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "照らす",
        "answer": "てらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ先",
        "answer": "まっさき"
    },
    {
        "question": "募集",
        "answer": "ぼしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "電柱",
        "answer": "でんちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "架空",
        "answer": "かくう"
    },
    {
        "question": "直線",
        "answer": "ちょくせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "下降",
        "answer": "かこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "問い合わせ",
        "answer": "といあわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼寝",
        "answer": "ひるね"
    },
    {
        "question": "寺院",
        "answer": "じいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "課税",
        "answer": "かぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "釜",
        "answer": "かま"
    },
    {
        "question": "単数",
        "answer": "たんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "発想",
        "answer": "はっそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "盗難",
        "answer": "とうなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "当日",
        "answer": "とうじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "兼ねる",
        "answer": "かねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "実感",
        "answer": "じっかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "頂点",
        "answer": "ちょうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "持参",
        "answer": "じさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "人造",
        "answer": "じんぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "中世",
        "answer": "ちゅうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "不運",
        "answer": "ふうん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一流",
        "answer": "いちりゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "転がる",
        "answer": "ころがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "吊る",
        "answer": "つる"
    },
    {
        "question": "特色",
        "answer": "とくしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "造船",
        "answer": "ぞうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "空中",
        "answer": "くうちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "勘違い",
        "answer": "かんちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "原料",
        "answer": "げんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "流行る",
        "answer": "はやる"
    },
    {
        "question": "学部",
        "answer": "がくぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "溜める",
        "answer": "ためる"
    },
    {
        "question": "売店",
        "answer": "ばいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "縮れる",
        "answer": "ちぢれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "引算",
        "answer": "ひきざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "見下ろす",
        "answer": "みおろす"
    },
    {
        "question": "足る",
        "answer": "たる"
    },
    {
        "question": "枕",
        "answer": "まくら"
    },
    {
        "question": "特定",
        "answer": "とくてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "年度",
        "answer": "ねんど"
    },
    {
        "question": "深夜",
        "answer": "しんや"
    },
    {
        "question": "電流",
        "answer": "でんりゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "特長",
        "answer": "とくちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "素直",
        "answer": "すなお"
    },
    {
        "question": "近付ける",
        "answer": "ちかづける"
    },
    {
        "question": "工員",
        "answer": "こういん"
    },
    {
        "question": "匙",
        "answer": "さじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "海水浴",
        "answer": "かいすいよく"
    },
    {
        "question": "女房",
        "answer": "にょうぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "灯油",
        "answer": "とうゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し訳ない",
        "answer": "もうしわけない"
    },
    {
        "question": "孝行",
        "answer": "こうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "斜め",
        "answer": "ななめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "噴火",
        "answer": "ふんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "出入り",
        "answer": "でいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "四季",
        "answer": "しき"
    },
    {
        "question": "内科",
        "answer": "ないか"
    },
    {
        "question": "推定",
        "answer": "すいてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "元々",
        "answer": "もともと"
    },
    {
        "question": "望遠鏡",
        "answer": "ぼうえんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "上旬",
        "answer": "じょうじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "厳重",
        "answer": "げんじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "著す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "複写",
        "answer": "ふくしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "反る",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "王女",
        "answer": "おうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "都心",
        "answer": "としん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恨む",
        "answer": "うらむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "本部",
        "answer": "ほんぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "区切る",
        "answer": "くぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "液体",
        "answer": "えきたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "鈍い",
        "answer": "にぶい"
    },
    {
        "question": "境界",
        "answer": "きょうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "群れ",
        "answer": "むれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "薄める",
        "answer": "うすめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "未満",
        "answer": "みまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "酢",
        "answer": "す"
    },
    {
        "question": "炭鉱",
        "answer": "たんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "接する",
        "answer": "せっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "子孫",
        "answer": "しそん"
    },
    {
        "question": "漸く",
        "answer": "ようやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "紙幣",
        "answer": "しへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "斬る",
        "answer": "きる"
    },
    {
        "question": "悔しい",
        "answer": "くやしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "逸れる",
        "answer": "それる"
    },
    {
        "question": "捩る",
        "answer": "ねじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "配る",
        "answer": "くばる"
    },
    {
        "question": "高度",
        "answer": "こうど"
    },
    {
        "question": "下駄",
        "answer": "げた"
    },
    {
        "question": "賞品",
        "answer": "しょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "積む",
        "answer": "つむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "瓶詰",
        "answer": "びんづめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "小便",
        "answer": "しょうべん"
    },
    {
        "question": "侵入",
        "answer": "しんにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "主語",
        "answer": "しゅご"
    },
    {
        "question": "摩擦",
        "answer": "まさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "小学生",
        "answer": "しょうがくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "曲げる",
        "answer": "まげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "図形",
        "answer": "ずけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "突き当たる",
        "answer": "つきあたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "上る",
        "answer": "のぼる"
    },
    {
        "question": "棄てる",
        "answer": "すてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "等分",
        "answer": "とうぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "差し引き",
        "answer": "さしひき"
    },
    {
        "question": "災難",
        "answer": "さいなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "話合い",
        "answer": "はなしあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "湯飲み",
        "answer": "ゆのみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "淡水",
        "answer": "たんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "通貨",
        "answer": "つうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "郡",
        "answer": "ぐん"
    },
    {
        "question": "出掛ける",
        "answer": "でかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "例外",
        "answer": "れいがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一応",
        "answer": "いちおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "坊や",
        "answer": "ぼうや"
    },
    {
        "question": "普及",
        "answer": "ふきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "交流",
        "answer": "こうりゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "水産",
        "answer": "すいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "算数",
        "answer": "さんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "高等",
        "answer": "こうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "鈴",
        "answer": "すず"
    },
    {
        "question": "役人",
        "answer": "やくにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "速力",
        "answer": "そくりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "体積",
        "answer": "たいせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "振り仮名",
        "answer": "ふりがな"
    },
    {
        "question": "耕地",
        "answer": "こうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "巻く",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "防犯",
        "answer": "ぼうはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "撒く",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "中指",
        "answer": "なかゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎度",
        "answer": "まいど"
    },
    {
        "question": "系統",
        "answer": "けいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆様",
        "answer": "さかさま"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾く",
        "answer": "かたむく"
    },
    {
        "question": "お参り",
        "answer": "おまいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "便所",
        "answer": "べんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "保健",
        "answer": "ほけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "叔父さん",
        "answer": "おじさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "道順",
        "answer": "みちじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "増大",
        "answer": "ぞうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "物置",
        "answer": "ものおき"
    },
    {
        "question": "公務",
        "answer": "こうむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一旦",
        "answer": "いったん"
    },
    {
        "question": "超える",
        "answer": "こえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "中身",
        "answer": "なかみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "風船",
        "answer": "ふうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "就任",
        "answer": "しゅうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "馴れる",
        "answer": "なれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "平気",
        "answer": "へいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "平仮名",
        "answer": "ひらがな"
    },
    {
        "question": "載せる",
        "answer": "のせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "和服",
        "answer": "わふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "上り",
        "answer": "のぼり"
    },
    {
        "question": "墨",
        "answer": "すみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "断水",
        "answer": "だんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺身",
        "answer": "さしみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "内線",
        "answer": "ないせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "中途",
        "answer": "ちゅうと"
    },
    {
        "question": "運河",
        "answer": "うんが"
    },
    {
        "question": "筆者",
        "answer": "ひっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "湯気",
        "answer": "ゆげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "活字",
        "answer": "かつじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "灯台",
        "answer": "とうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦心",
        "answer": "くしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜間",
        "answer": "やかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "蒔く",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "生け花",
        "answer": "いけばな"
    },
    {
        "question": "流石",
        "answer": "さすが"
    },
    {
        "question": "日時",
        "answer": "にちじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "扇風機",
        "answer": "せんぷうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝記",
        "answer": "でんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "塊",
        "answer": "かたまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "煉瓦",
        "answer": "れんが"
    },
    {
        "question": "鳴らす",
        "answer": "ならす"
    },
    {
        "question": "揃う",
        "answer": "そろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "血圧",
        "answer": "けつあつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "速達",
        "answer": "そくたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "紫",
        "answer": "むらさき"
    },
    {
        "question": "名所",
        "answer": "めいしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶く",
        "answer": "とく"
    },
    {
        "question": "噴水",
        "answer": "ふんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "混ぜる",
        "answer": "まぜる"
    },
    {
        "question": "討つ",
        "answer": "うつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宛名",
        "answer": "あてな"
    },
    {
        "question": "建つ",
        "answer": "たつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "車掌",
        "answer": "しゃしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "憎らしい",
        "answer": "にくらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "砕く",
        "answer": "くだく"
    },
    {
        "question": "問答",
        "answer": "もんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "汚す",
        "answer": "よごす"
    },
    {
        "question": "浮かべる",
        "answer": "うかべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "繋がり",
        "answer": "つながり"
    },
    {
        "question": "助かる",
        "answer": "たすかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "寮",
        "answer": "りょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "田ぼ",
        "answer": "たんぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "発電",
        "answer": "はつでん"
    },
    {
        "question": "但し",
        "answer": "ただし"
    },
    {
        "question": "近々",
        "answer": "ちかぢか"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯車",
        "answer": "はぐるま"
    },
    {
        "question": "丼",
        "answer": "どんぶり"
    },
    {
        "question": "拡充",
        "answer": "かくじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "店屋",
        "answer": "みせや"
    },
    {
        "question": "着ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "臨時",
        "answer": "りんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽器",
        "answer": "がっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "窓口",
        "answer": "まどぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "破く",
        "answer": "やぶく"
    },
    {
        "question": "長短",
        "answer": "ちょうたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "広場",
        "answer": "ひろば"
    },
    {
        "question": "生意気",
        "answer": "なまいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛る",
        "answer": "もる"
    },
    {
        "question": "撫でる",
        "answer": "なでる"
    },
    {
        "question": "街角",
        "answer": "まちかど"
    },
    {
        "question": "下水",
        "answer": "げすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "解説",
        "answer": "かいせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄砲",
        "answer": "てっぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "こうして",
        "answer": "こうして"
    },
    {
        "question": "載る",
        "answer": "のる"
    },
    {
        "question": "美容",
        "answer": "びよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "面積",
        "answer": "めんせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "じゅうたん",
        "answer": "（カーペット）"
    },
    {
        "question": "巡査",
        "answer": "じゅんさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片仮名",
        "answer": "かたかな"
    },
    {
        "question": "再三",
        "answer": "さいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕える",
        "answer": "とらえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "催促",
        "answer": "さいそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "待ち合わせる",
        "answer": "まちあわせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "相違",
        "answer": "そうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "気配",
        "answer": "けはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "開通",
        "answer": "かいつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "超す",
        "answer": "こす"
    },
    {
        "question": "為替",
        "answer": "かわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "公式",
        "answer": "こうしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "電力",
        "answer": "でんりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "概論",
        "answer": "がいろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生える",
        "answer": "はえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "日帰り",
        "answer": "ひがえり"
    },
    {
        "question": "満点",
        "answer": "まんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "正面",
        "answer": "しょうめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "削る",
        "answer": "けずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "量る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "知合い",
        "answer": "しりあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "区分",
        "answer": "くぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "洒落",
        "answer": "しゃれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大通り",
        "answer": "おおどおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "金魚",
        "answer": "きんぎょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "各自",
        "answer": "かくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自習",
        "answer": "じしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "名作",
        "answer": "めいさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ込む",
        "answer": "ひっこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "各地",
        "answer": "かくち"
    },
    {
        "question": "撮影",
        "answer": "さつえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "調整",
        "answer": "ちょうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "功績",
        "answer": "こうせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕る",
        "answer": "とる"
    },
    {
        "question": "無地",
        "answer": "むじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "公害",
        "answer": "こうがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "資料",
        "answer": "しりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "研修",
        "answer": "けんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "税関",
        "answer": "ぜいかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "突く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "下る",
        "answer": "くだる"
    },
    {
        "question": "引返す",
        "answer": "ひきかえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "四角",
        "answer": "しかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "将棋",
        "answer": "しょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "加熱",
        "answer": "かねつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "儲ける",
        "answer": "もうける"
    },
    {
        "question": "含める",
        "answer": "ふくめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "学力",
        "answer": "がくりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "陽射",
        "answer": "ひざし"
    },
    {
        "question": "呼び出す",
        "answer": "よびだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "塵芥",
        "answer": "ごみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "採点",
        "answer": "さいてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "涼む",
        "answer": "すずむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "書留",
        "answer": "かきとめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集合",
        "answer": "しゅうごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "規準",
        "answer": "きじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "特売",
        "answer": "とくばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "外れる",
        "answer": "はずれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "為す",
        "answer": "なす"
    },
    {
        "question": "自然科学",
        "answer": "しぜんかがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "敬う",
        "answer": "うやまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "待合室",
        "answer": "まちあいしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "銘々",
        "answer": "めいめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "澄む",
        "answer": "すむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "客席",
        "answer": "きゃくせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕日",
        "answer": "ゆうひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "狙い",
        "answer": "ねらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛糸",
        "answer": "けいと"
    },
    {
        "question": "過半数",
        "answer": "かはんすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "寿命",
        "answer": "じゅみょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾かす",
        "answer": "かわかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "基礎",
        "answer": "きそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "櫛",
        "answer": "くし"
    },
    {
        "question": "追加",
        "answer": "ついか"
    },
    {
        "question": "校舎",
        "answer": "こうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "適確",
        "answer": "てきかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "対策",
        "answer": "たいさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "繋がる",
        "answer": "つながる"
    },
    {
        "question": "頭脳",
        "answer": "ずのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "家主",
        "answer": "やぬし"
    },
    {
        "question": "利害",
        "answer": "りがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆さ",
        "answer": "さかさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "評論",
        "answer": "ひょうろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "能率",
        "answer": "のうりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "至急",
        "answer": "しきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "迫る",
        "answer": "せまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "燃やす",
        "answer": "もやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "始めに",
        "answer": "はじめに"
    },
    {
        "question": "塩辛い",
        "answer": "しおからい"
    },
    {
        "question": "水素",
        "answer": "すいそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "補う",
        "answer": "おぎなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "車庫",
        "answer": "しゃこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬品",
        "answer": "やくひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "浴衣",
        "answer": "ゆかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "再来週",
        "answer": "さらいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "踏切",
        "answer": "ふみきり"
    },
    {
        "question": "成分",
        "answer": "せいぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "大木",
        "answer": "たいぼく"
    },
    {
        "question": "障子",
        "answer": "しょうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "定規",
        "answer": "じょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "電波",
        "answer": "でんぱ"
    },
    {
        "question": "酸性",
        "answer": "さんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "展開",
        "answer": "てんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "御無沙汰",
        "answer": "ごぶさた"
    },
    {
        "question": "御辞儀",
        "answer": "おじぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中年",
        "answer": "ちゅうねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "水平",
        "answer": "すいへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "相互",
        "answer": "そうご"
    },
    {
        "question": "武士",
        "answer": "ぶし"
    },
    {
        "question": "属する",
        "answer": "ぞくする"
    },
    {
        "question": "感想",
        "answer": "かんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "足跡",
        "answer": "あしあと"
    },
    {
        "question": "便箋",
        "answer": "びんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "休業",
        "answer": "きゅうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "遡る",
        "answer": "さかのぼる"
    },
    {
        "question": "体操",
        "answer": "たいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "投書",
        "answer": "とうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貸家",
        "answer": "かしや"
    },
    {
        "question": "三角",
        "answer": "さんかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "矛盾",
        "answer": "むじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "斜",
        "answer": "はす"
    },
    {
        "question": "朗らか",
        "answer": "ほがらか"
    },
    {
        "question": "田植え",
        "answer": "たうえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ掛かる",
        "answer": "ひっかかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "順々",
        "answer": "じゅんじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "溶ける",
        "answer": "とける"
    },
    {
        "question": "先頭",
        "answer": "せんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "緯度",
        "answer": "いど"
    },
    {
        "question": "祝日",
        "answer": "しゅくじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "白髪",
        "answer": "しらが"
    },
    {
        "question": "作成",
        "answer": "さくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿度",
        "answer": "しつど"
    },
    {
        "question": "停車",
        "answer": "ていしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "破片",
        "answer": "はへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "×",
        "answer": "ばつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "温室",
        "answer": "おんしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "暴れる",
        "answer": "あばれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "乱暴",
        "answer": "らんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "懐かしい",
        "answer": "なつかしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "生長",
        "answer": "せいちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "庖丁",
        "answer": "ほうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "羨ましい",
        "answer": "うらやましい"
    },
    {
        "question": "改造",
        "answer": "かいぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掘る",
        "answer": "ほる"
    },
    {
        "question": "落着く",
        "answer": "おちつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "交じる",
        "answer": "まじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "専制",
        "answer": "せんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "増やす",
        "answer": "ふやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "目下",
        "answer": "めした"
    },
    {
        "question": "隔てる",
        "answer": "へだてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "花嫁",
        "answer": "はなよめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名物",
        "answer": "めいぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬指",
        "answer": "くすりゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "高級",
        "answer": "こうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "見付ける",
        "answer": "みつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯磨き",
        "answer": "はみがき"
    },
    {
        "question": "氏名",
        "answer": "しめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ͼ立",
        "answer": "たいりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "育児",
        "answer": "いくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "温帯",
        "answer": "おんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "針路",
        "answer": "しんろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "凸凹",
        "answer": "でこぼこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "在る",
        "answer": "ある"
    },
    {
        "question": "一休み",
        "answer": "ひとやすみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "分類",
        "answer": "ぶんるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "応ずる",
        "answer": "おうずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "肯定",
        "answer": "こうてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼稚",
        "answer": "ようち"
    },
    {
        "question": "埋める",
        "answer": "うめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "短所",
        "answer": "たんしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "活躍",
        "answer": "かつやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "船便",
        "answer": "ふなびん"
    },
    {
        "question": "慰める",
        "answer": "なぐさめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ黒",
        "answer": "まっくろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引受る",
        "answer": "ひきうける"
    },
    {
        "question": "過程",
        "answer": "かてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "仮名遣い",
        "answer": "かなづかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "移転",
        "answer": "いてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "余計",
        "answer": "よけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "捻る",
        "answer": "ひねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "上下",
        "answer": "じょうげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "味わう",
        "answer": "あじわう"
    },
    {
        "question": "堅い",
        "answer": "かたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "四捨五入",
        "answer": "ししゃごにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "碁",
        "answer": "ご"
    },
    {
        "question": "記号",
        "answer": "きごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "通り掛かる",
        "answer": "とおりかかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "平野",
        "answer": "へいや"
    },
    {
        "question": "警備",
        "answer": "けいび"
    },
    {
        "question": "直角",
        "answer": "ちょっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "紙屑",
        "answer": "かみくず"
    },
    {
        "question": "稽古",
        "answer": "けいこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "振舞う",
        "answer": "ふるまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "重点",
        "answer": "じゅうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "包装",
        "answer": "ほうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "要旨",
        "answer": "ようし"
    },
    {
        "question": "用途",
        "answer": "ようと"
    },
    {
        "question": "関東",
        "answer": "かんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "放る",
        "answer": "ほうる"
    },
    {
        "question": "貨物",
        "answer": "かもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "広々",
        "answer": "ひろびろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "国籍",
        "answer": "こくせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "代名詞",
        "answer": "だいめいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "給与",
        "answer": "きゅうよ"
    },
    {
        "question": "話中",
        "answer": "はなしちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "寸法",
        "answer": "すんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "浸ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "吊す",
        "answer": "つるす"
    },
    {
        "question": "擦る",
        "answer": "こする"
    },
    {
        "question": "器械",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "冠",
        "answer": "かんむり"
    },
    {
        "question": "案外",
        "answer": "あんがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "重量",
        "answer": "じゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "外科",
        "answer": "げか"
    },
    {
        "question": "南米",
        "answer": "なんべい"
    },
    {
        "question": "蛇口",
        "answer": "じゃぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "直流",
        "answer": "ちょくりゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "清掃",
        "answer": "せいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "整数",
        "answer": "せいすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "占う",
        "answer": "うらなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "屑",
        "answer": "くず"
    },
    {
        "question": "一昨年",
        "answer": "いっさくねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "工事",
        "answer": "こうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "副詞",
        "answer": "ふくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "執筆",
        "answer": "しっぴつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "材木",
        "answer": "ざいもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "琴",
        "answer": "こと"
    },
    {
        "question": "高層",
        "answer": "こうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "楕円",
        "answer": "だえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "列島",
        "answer": "れっとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "法則",
        "answer": "ほうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "遊園地",
        "answer": "ゆうえんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "恨み",
        "answer": "うらみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "蓄える",
        "answer": "たくわえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "要領",
        "answer": "ようりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "目印",
        "answer": "めじるし"
    },
    {
        "question": "匂う",
        "answer": "におう"
    },
    {
        "question": "物語る",
        "answer": "ものがたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "亡くす",
        "answer": "なくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "売買",
        "answer": "ばいばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "解放",
        "answer": "かいほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "例える",
        "answer": "たとえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "和英",
        "answer": "わえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "円い",
        "answer": "まるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "混じる",
        "answer": "まじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "英文",
        "answer": "えいぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "焦点",
        "answer": "しょうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "反省",
        "answer": "はんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "機関車",
        "answer": "きかんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "個所",
        "answer": "かしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "石鹸",
        "answer": "せっけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "被せる",
        "answer": "かぶせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "灰色",
        "answer": "はいいろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷める",
        "answer": "さめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉱物",
        "answer": "こうぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "接近",
        "answer": "せっきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "下線",
        "answer": "かせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "気体",
        "answer": "きたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱線",
        "answer": "だっせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "脂",
        "answer": "あぶら"
    },
    {
        "question": "製作",
        "answer": "せいさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "看板",
        "answer": "かんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "葬式",
        "answer": "そうしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "肘",
        "answer": "ひじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貸間",
        "answer": "かしま"
    },
    {
        "question": "実物",
        "answer": "じつぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集会",
        "answer": "しゅうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "圧縮",
        "answer": "あっしゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "神話",
        "answer": "しんわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "片寄る",
        "answer": "かたよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "合理",
        "answer": "ごうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "車輪",
        "answer": "しゃりん"
    },
    {
        "question": "正方形",
        "answer": "せいほうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "区域",
        "answer": "くいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "戸棚",
        "answer": "とだな"
    },
    {
        "question": "湿気",
        "answer": "しっけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ青",
        "answer": "まっさお"
    },
    {
        "question": "下旬",
        "answer": "げじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "私立",
        "answer": "しりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "指定",
        "answer": "してい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一段と",
        "answer": "いちだんと"
    },
    {
        "question": "落第",
        "answer": "らくだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "長女",
        "answer": "ちょうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "削除",
        "answer": "さくじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "反映",
        "answer": "はんえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "片道",
        "answer": "かたみち"
    },
    {
        "question": "出来上がり",
        "answer": "できあがり"
    },
    {
        "question": "交通機関",
        "answer": "こうつうきかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "膨大",
        "answer": "ぼうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "姓",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "符号",
        "answer": "ふごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "羊毛",
        "answer": "ようもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "感ずる",
        "answer": "かんずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "見送る",
        "answer": "みおくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "掛け算",
        "answer": "かけざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "缶詰",
        "answer": "かんづめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "初めに",
        "answer": "はじめに"
    },
    {
        "question": "各々",
        "answer": "おのおの"
    },
    {
        "question": "人差指",
        "answer": "ひとさしゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "公表",
        "answer": "こうひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "盆地",
        "answer": "ぼんち"
    },
    {
        "question": "姿勢",
        "answer": "しせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "先々月",
        "answer": "せんせんげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "四つ角",
        "answer": "よつかど"
    },
    {
        "question": "目次",
        "answer": "もくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "覗く",
        "answer": "のぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "貝",
        "answer": "かい"
    },
    {
        "question": "立ち止まる",
        "answer": "たちどまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "焦げる",
        "answer": "こげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "基地",
        "answer": "きち"
    },
    {
        "question": "剥す",
        "answer": "はがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "殖やす",
        "answer": "ふやす"
    },
    {
        "question": "小数",
        "answer": "しょうすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "崩れる",
        "answer": "くずれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲直り",
        "answer": "なかなおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "着々",
        "answer": "ちゃくちゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "茂る",
        "answer": "しげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "実例",
        "answer": "じつれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "勝敗",
        "answer": "しょうはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼稚園",
        "answer": "ようちえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "末っ子",
        "answer": "すえっこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "身分",
        "answer": "みぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "抽象",
        "answer": "ちゅうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "麓",
        "answer": "ふもと"
    },
    {
        "question": "索引",
        "answer": "さくいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "講師",
        "answer": "こうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "自治",
        "answer": "じち"
    },
    {
        "question": "日程",
        "answer": "にってい"
    },
    {
        "question": "凍える",
        "answer": "こごえる"
    }
]